Ethereum was built to be a sort of new and improved version of Bitcoin
イーサリアムは、ビットコインの新しい改良版として として開発されました。
and to do things Bitcoin couldn't do
ビットコインができないこともできるよう なっています。
Original aim of Ethereum was to create not just a decentralized money
イーサリアムのオリジナル目的は、ただ 分散型のお金を作成することだけでなく
but essentially a decentralized global computer
本質的には、分散型グローバルコンピュータをつくることでした
that could do computational problems
それは計算問題を処理することができます。
Ethereum has its own currency Ether
イーサリアムは独自の通貨イーサ―を持っています
The Ether are really there to service as a sort-of gas
イーサーは、有る意味サービスを提供するためのガソリンです。
for the computations that are going on on this  network  of computers that run Ethereum
イーサリアムを実行するコンピュータたちのネットワーク上で起こっている 計算処理のためのガソリンです。
TRUST DISRUPTED BITCOIN AND THE BLOCKCHAIN TechCrunch  Originals
TRUST破砕 ビットコインとBLOCKCHAIN TechCrunch Oriiginals
5. Ethereum's Blockchain
5.イーサリアムのブロックチェイン
July 30,2015: Release date of the first live version of Ethereum $160 Million : Peak value of Ether raised by the Decentralized Autonomous Organization(DAO) $50 Million : Value of Ether stolen in a hack on the DAO
2015年7月30日：イーサリアム の最初のライブバージョンのリリース日 160億円 :自律分散機構（DAO）にファンディングされたイーサーのピーク価格 50億円：DAOのハックで盗まれたイーサの価値
The original reason I like the name is that Ether was
私がイーザーという名前がすきなもともとの理由は
VITALIK BUTERIN, FOUNDER ETHEREUM,TORONTO MOSCOW SHANGHAI This is a sort of thing  the scientist hypothesizing about it  in 19 century people were thinking
ヴィタリック ブテリン、イーサリアム創設者、トロント、モスクワ、上海 これは、人々が考えていた事の並べ替え19世紀にそれについての仮定の科学者 です
They hypothesize the existence of medium  kind-of permeates the entire universe
****光の波が通って移動するので、どのような水を通って移動- します彼らは、媒体の種類-のの存在は宇宙全体に浸透して仮説を立て
That in itself is  a kind of invisible
自体に目に見えないの一種であることを
but It provides us kind-of a global reference frame.
しかしそれ種類-のグローバル参照フレームを提供してくれます。
It is in some sense ,you-know,sort-of the base the universe runs on.
それはあなた知る、ある意味であり、ソートのベース宇宙は上で実行されます。
And actually I felt that was kind-of fitting analogy for what I wanted to do
そして、実際に私はそれは私がやりたいことのためにフィッティング類推種類-のだと感じました
Bitcoin has the wrong approach.
ビットコインは間違ったアプローチを持っています。
I would say Ethereum boasts features and opportunity to do the thing Bitcoin doesn't .
私はイーサリアムは、機能とビットコイン- がないことを行う機会を誇って言うでしょう。
It's like saying that a telephone can beat an orange.
それは電話がオレンジ色に倒すことができるというようなものです。
JOSEPH LUBIN, FOUNDER CONSENSYS,ETHEREUM CONSULTING FIRM,NEW YORK Ethererum is a decentralized application platform.
JOSEPHルビンは、創設者のCONSENSYS、イーサリアムコンサルティング会社は、NEW YORK Ethererumは、分散型アプリケーションプラットフォームです。
for transmission and storage of value
その親、ビットコインは、プラットフォームの詳細です値の送信および保管のために
So Bitcoin was essentially an experiment in monetary theory gone wildly successful
だから、ビットコインは基本的に大成- 功を収めてしまっ金融理論で実験しました
You can think of ethereum as the decentralized world wide web.
あなたは、分散型のワールド・ワイド・ウェブなどイーサリアムと考えることができます。
It will eventually be able to run all the different kinds of applications
最終的にはアプリケーションのすべての- 種類を実行することができるようになります
that we see on the World wide web
我々はワールドワイドウェブ上で見ること
The end of the day , it's kind-of fabric for **** you could almost describe it as a new Internet Infrastructure
一日の終わりには、それは一種-の_ ****あなたはほとんど 新しいインターネットインフラとしてそれを記述することができるための布であります
Eventually it runs Facebook-like application
結局それはFacebookのようなアプリケーションを実行
All the differences that would be Peer-to-Peer
ピアツーピアであろうすべての違い
ownership of data , ownership of communication or informational emissions
サーバ・クライアント型のアーキテクチャではなく、分散化データ、通信または情報の排出量の所有権の所有権
will rest with  the users of the system rather than owners like  the company like Facebook
システムのユーザではなく、Faceb- ookのような会社のような所有者で休むます
I think Vitalik knows what he is building
私はVitalikは彼が構築されていることを知っていると思います
a giant globally distributed re-programmable supercomputer
巨大なグローバルに分散し、再プログラム可能なスーパーコンピュータ
on the  scale of the mankind never seen before
人類の規模で前に見たことがありません
which initially supports this concept of  Smart Contracts
そして彼はメカニズムを介してそれをやっています最初にスマート契約のこの概念をサポートしています
and issues a token  just like Bitcoin
とちょうどビットコインのようなトークンを発行
So there is a value being created by the  mining that we are doing.
だから我々がやっているマイニングによって作成された値が存在します。
THe biggest differences that ethererum produces mines
ethererumが地雷を生産する最大の違い
that are reprogrammable to tasks that we don’t necessary know what they are gonna do yet
私たちは必要な彼らがつもりです何か知- ってまだないタスクに再プログラム可能です
One of the highest ambitions of  Ethereum from the beginning
最初からイーサリアムの最高野望の一つ
was that you would actually be able to program
あなたが実際にプログラムすることができるだろうということでした
the functioning of entire corporations
全体の企業の機能
into this global computer
このグローバルコンピュータに
And You would have not just a decentralized currency but decentralized company
そして、あなただけの_分権通貨を_が、分散型企業ではないだろう
that would run according to the rules that you have programed into this network
あなたがこのネットワークにプログ- ラムされている規則に従って実行されます
so there was always this idea that Ethereum might allow what people called Decentralized Autonomous Organization
ので、このアイデアはイーサリアムは、人々が自律分散組織と呼ばれるもの できる可能性があることを 常にありました
So Decentralized Autonomous Organization ,
だから自律分散組織、
This idea that you can have kind-of *automatons* that are written in code  that set on the blockchain
あなたは親切な-のblockchainに設定されたコードで書かれています*オートマトン* を持つことができることこのアイデア
could be like some voting mechanism, could be voting by projection markets or some other new thing
という点で、あなたは、スマート契約を通じて支配します _は_または他のいくつかの新しいものプロジェクション市場により投票することができ、いくつかの投票メカニズムのようなものでした
would be sort-of a company that would be run not according to human decision making
ソートの人間の意思決定によらないで実行される会社になります
and human rules ,but  Instead  according to rules that you programed into Ethereum network.
と人間のルールが、代わりにあなたがイーサリアムネットワークにプログラムされたルールに従って。
It can actually  leave the decision making up to an Artificial Intelligence
これは、実際に人工知能までの意思決定を残すことができます
So if you would have a board ,you can basically say ,hey we  can't come to the consensus
あなたがボードを持っているならば、あなたは基本的に言うことができるだから、ちょっと我々は合意に来ることができません
so, let's just refer this to AI
ので、ちょうどAIにこれを参照してみましょう
and everyone just delegates the roles to robots and robots make decision for them
と誰も彼らのために意思決定を行うロボットやロボットに委譲役割
then eventually you can imagine that many boards are just run by AI.
その後、最終的には、多くのボードがちょうどAIによって運営されていることを想像することができます。
and occasionally intervene by humans
と時折人間が介入します
DAO attracted something like 150 million dollars
DAOを150万ドルのようなものを集めて
in the course of a little over a month
月強のコースで
basically on the first days that it was operational
基本的にそれが動作したことを最初の日に
that basically siphoned about the half of the money into an account under the control of the attacker
あなたが入ってきたこの攻撃を持っていたような方法で契約を活用するためにうまく管理しました基本的に攻撃者の制御下で、口座にお金の約半分を吸い上げていること
one saving grace in this attack
この攻撃に恵みを保存する1
was that money that was siphoned off
吸い上げたそのお金でした
because of the way the DAO was written couldn't  be used for 30days
ため、DAOが書かれた方法のは30- 日のために使用することができませんでした
to try to figure out how to stop the attacker from getting control of 60 million dollars
ので、このカウントダウンは始まりました6000万ドルの制御を得ることから、攻撃者を停止する方法を見つけ出すしようとします
so we have this time in order to see to determine whether we gonna do something about it or where we just going to let it.
私たちは私たちが何かそれについてか、我々はそれをさせるつもりを行う- つもりかどうかを判断するために参照するために、この時間を持っています。
I don’t think that Ethereum  has the balls to leave the fact as is.
私はイーサリアムがあるとして事実を残すためにボールを持っているとは思いません。
are you hard-forking the entire blockchain?
あなたは全体blockchainをハードフォークされていますか？
It set off this really pretty philosophical debate about
それは約これは本当にかなり哲学的な議論をオフに設定
how to deal with the problem like this
このような問題に対処する方法
in the realm of smart contracts and virtual currency
スマート契約や仮想通貨の領域で
was that this record of transactions going back in time could never been changed
あなたはビットコインとイーサリアムた、blockchain技術との素晴らしい観光スポットの一つを参照してください。 時間に遡ってこのトランザクションのレコードが変更されていないということでした
that is one of the reason that this is  so valuable
それは、これはとても貴重であることを理由の一つであります
you could look back and know that a transaction happened know that nobody could temper with that ,nobody could change it
あなたが振り返ると、トランザクションが誰もそれと気性ができなかったことを知- って起こった、誰もがそれを変更することができなかったことを知っている可能性があり
once you had a DAO , people wanted to go back and change this contract
あなたはDAOを持っていたら、人々は戻って、この契約を変更したいです
so that the person who seized all this money
ようにすべてのこのお金を押収した人
that those transactions wouldn't be valid
これらのトランザクションが有効ではないことを
but it struck at the very core of what the Ethereum was supposed to be.
それはイーサリアムをすることになっていたものの非常にコアで打ちました。